This video is sponsored by Wren.
本视频由 Wren 赞助。
Is love in art? Then it requires knowledge, and effort. Or is love a pleasant sensation, which to
爱是艺术吗？那么，它就需要知识和努力。还是说爱是一种快感，
experience is a matter of chance... something one falls into if one is lucky? This little book is
能体验到是偶然的……运气好会落入其中？
based on the former premise, while undoubtedly the majority of people today believe in the latter.
这本小书是建立在我刚刚提到的第一个可能，而今天的大多数人相信第二个可能。
not that people think that love is not important. They are starved for it. They watch endless numbers
不是说人们认为爱情不重要。其实，他们非常渴望爱情。
of films and happy and unhappy love stories. They listen to hundreds of trashy songs about love. Yet
他们看许多的电影关于快乐和不快乐的爱情故事。他们听数百首关于爱情的垃圾歌曲。
hardly anyone thinks that there's anything that needs to be learned about love. Scrolling through
但是，几乎没有人认为关于爱情有什么需要学习的。 现在 每天看
posts about romantic relationships nowadays, I kind of hate it. Not because I'm a cynic or I find PDA
关浪漫爱情的帖文，我有点讨厌它。不是因为我是一个愤世嫉俗的人，或者我觉得 PDA
to be cringy. In fact, I love, love. I think it should be central to the way we live our lives. But there
很冷漠。其实，我爱，爱。我认为它应该成为我们生活方式的核心。但是
are several beliefs about romantic relationships that i see commonly floating around on the
，我经常在互联网上看到一些关于浪漫关系的信念，
internet that bug me. There's the "if you wanted to he would" group, the "never settle" advocates,
这些信念让我很不舒服。有“如果他愿意，他就会” 的群体，“永不解决”的倡导者，
the constant talk about "red flags" and "standards" and letting random strangers on TikTok make you
不断谈论 “危险信号” 和 “标准”，让 TikTok 上的随机陌生人让你
question your healthy relationship. "You don't find that suspicious... you don't find that suspicious??"
觉得你的健康的恋爱觉得很可疑。 “你不觉得可疑……你不觉得可疑？？”
As a preface, I'll probably talk more so about things I see and hear from straight
作为序言，我可能谈论的大部分都是我从异性恋
women since that's what I identify as. But the fundamental concepts that I talk about for love do
女性那里看到和听到的事情，因为这就是我所认同的。但我所说的关于爱情的基本概念确实
apply to all romantic relationships, regardless of gender or sexuality. Before I get to specific
适用于所有浪漫关系，无论性别或性取向如何。在谈到我在网上看到的
content I see online, let's talk about two broader questions. Is love passive or active? In other words,
内容之前，让我们先谈谈两个更广泛的问题。爱是被动的还是主动的？换句话说，
is love a state that exists independently and is waiting for us to fall into, or does it require
爱是一种独立存在的状态，等待着我们陷入，还是需要
our participation and effort to bring about? Two, is our conception of love grounded in anything real,
我们的参与和努力才能实现？第二，我们对爱的概念是基于任何真实的东西，
or are we comparing our relationships to hyper real love? Now we can't love if we're all dead
还是我们将我们的关系与超真实的爱进行比较？现在，如果我们都死于
from climate change, right? Smooth segway into a sponsorship... I know... Well i'm here to briefly talk
气候变化，我们就不能爱了，对吧？顺利进入赞助商...我知道...好吧，我在这里简要谈谈
about Wren. Wren is a website where you can take a short quiz to calculate your carbon footprint
Wren。 Wren 是一个网站，您可以在其中做一个简短的测验来计算您的碳足迹
and find ways to reduce it. They have multiple carbon reduction projects that you can help
和找到减少碳足迹的方法。他们有多个碳减排项目，您可以
fund such as tree planting, mineral weathering, and rainforest protection.
资助这些项目，例如种树、矿物风化和雨林保护。
Once you sign up to make a monthly contribution to offset your carbon footprint, you receive
一旦您注册每月捐款以抵消您的碳足迹，您就会收到
monthly updates about the projects you support. You get to see what your money is spent on with
有关您支持的项目的每月更新。 您可以通过
photos and details of every tree planted, every acre reforested, and every ton of carbon offset.
种植的每棵树、每英亩重新造林，和每吨碳抵消，的照片来了解您的钱花在了哪些地方 。
Check out the link in the description box for more info. The first 100 people who sign up using
查看描述框中的链接以获取更多信息。使用我的链接注册的前 100 人
my link will have 10 extra trees planted in their name! Thank you again, Wren for sponsoring this video.
将以他们的名义额外种植 10 棵树！再次感谢 Wren 赞助此视频。
Okay, so first, is love passive or active? Based on the quote I recited at the beginning of the video,
好的，首先，爱是被动的还是主动的？根据我在视频开头引用的那句话，
you can probably guess that I believe love is active. I want to be clear, a lot of the things
您可能会猜到我相信爱是活跃的。我想明确一点说，
that I will be saying in this section of the video can be found in Eric Fromm's the Art of Loving.
我在视频的这一部分说的很多东西都可以在 Eric Fromm 的《爱的艺术》中找到。
It was written in 1956, so obviously some of the things are outdated but I still feel as though a
它写于 1956 年，所以当然有些东西已经过时了，但我还是感觉其中有
lot of it is applicable to present day. See Fromm notices that most people view love through a
很多内容很适合今天。 Fromm 注意到大多数人通过
passive lens. Love is somehow out there waiting for us to stumble upon. You hear phrases such
被动的视角看待爱情。爱就在外面等着我们偶然发现。我们唱会听到诸如
as "true love comes to those who wait" "do not chase love. It will just find you when the time is right"
“真正的爱会找到等待的人” “不要追逐爱情。它会在适当的时候找到你” 这样的短语 ，
and so people focus on making themselves as lovable as possible rather than loving.
因此很多人就会关注在于让自己变得越来越可爱，容易被爱，就忘了注意到好好去爱。
Fromm likens dating to modern capitalism, modern capitalism works on the premise of mutually beneficial
Fromm 把约会比作现代资本主义。现代资本主义是在互利
exchange. I buy your product and you get my money. To participate in the dating world is to place
交换的前提下运作的。我买你的产品，你得到我的钱。参与约会世界就是将
yourself in what Fromm calls the personality market. You try to make yourself as lovable as possible
自己置身于弗洛姆所说的 “个性市场。” 你是这让自己变得越可爱越好，
which is really dependent on the time period and culture. For a long time, the dream man was
“可爱” 其实都是会跟着时间一起改变。长期以来，很对人最理想的男人
ambitious, physically strong, a protector. But now there's a lot more demand for men who crochet and
很有动力，身体强壮，是保护者。 但是现在对钩针编织并且 会哭到我们肩膀上
will cry into our shoulders. A lot of people also try to make themselves lovable for certain types
的男人有更多的需求 。 很多人也试图让自己对某些类型
of people. For example, if Person 1 wants a goth tiddy  gf and Person 2 wants a computer science
的人觉得可爱。例如，如果第 1 个人想要一个 “goth tiddy"女友，而第 2 个人想要一个计算机科学
boy, they're probably going to dress differently and get well versed in different talking points.
男孩，他们应该会穿不同的衣服并精通不同的谈话要点。
But by then, they've already become selective about which market they're putting themselves out onto.
但到那时，他们已经开始选择将自己投入到到哪个市场。
They are already deciding what kind of love should come their way and so really love becomes what
他们已经在决定什么样的爱应该往他们的方向出现，所以真正的爱成为
will satisfy your desire to not be lonely. Fromm compares this self-interested search for a partner
满足你不想孤独的愿望的东西。弗洛姆将这种自私的寻找合作伙伴
to a bargain, because you can almost think of it like a graph. You have fallen in love when you
比作讨价还价，因为你几乎可以把它想象成一个图表。 当你
find the optimal sweet spot between social value and desire for you. This strategical exchange
在社会价值和对你的渴望之间找到最佳平衡点 时，你就坠入爱河 了。 这种交流
doesn't really treat people as people. Instead, we become commodities on this personality market
并没有真正把人视为人。相反，我们成为这个个性市场上的商品，
and we're all trying to increase our market value by adhering to what others want. I know a lot of
我们都在努力通过坚持别人想要的来增加我们的市场价值。我知道很多
straight women are happy and think it's quite progressive that more straight men are moving
异性恋 女性都很开心，并且认为越来越多的异性恋男性正在
from a Alpha gymbro lifestyle, to adopting more nerdy soft or feminine traits. I see so many
从 Alpha gymbro 生活方式变得拥有跟多 “书呆子” 或女性化的特征，这是相当进步的。我看到很多
comments being like "Oh, men are finally listening to what women want!" And don't get me wrong,
评论就像 “哦，男人终于听女人想要什么了！” 不要误会我的意思，
I definitely prefer the latter type of men as well, but should we really be happy about this? Like the
我当然也更喜欢后一种类型的男人，但我们真的应该为此感到高兴吗？
men are just adhering to changing social values to be more desirable on this personality market.
就像男人只是在追一直在变化的社会价值观，以便在这个个性市场上更受欢迎。
But is a man who is traditionally masculine necessarily a worse lover than a man written
但是一个传统上是男性的男人就一定比一个更女性化的男人更糟糕吗？
by a woman? Instead of congratulating people for becoming a better commodity to soothe our
与其祝贺别人成为更好的商品来抚慰我们
awareness of our existential loneliness, why do we not focus on loving itself? This is what I mean by
对存在孤独的意识，我们为什么不专注于爱自己呢？这就是我所说的
passive versus active conceptions of love. Someone who thinks of love passively asks "How do I become
被动与主动的爱的概念。觉得爱情是被动的人会问，“我如何被爱？“
loved? Someone who thinks of love actively asks "How do I love?" When relationships end, people tend
觉得爱情是主动的人就会问，”我如何爱？“ 当关系结束时，人们往往
to focus on how to improve their lovability by working out, getting their hair done, buying new
会专注于如何变得更可爱，通过某种凡事想运动，剪头发，买新
clothes, advancing their career as exemplified by post-breakup glow-up videos on Youtube.
衣服, 提升自己的职业, 就像 Youtube 上的 “分手后发光” 视频一样。
"I'm gonna have a post-breakup glow-up, basically just doing my hair and makeup." "So we're going to get my
“我会做一个分手后的发光, 基本上只是做头发和化妆。” “所以我们要去做头发，
hair done, I'm going to self tan. We're going to whiten my teeth, we're going to do a face mask
我要自己晒黑。我们要美白牙齿，我们要做面膜
exfoliate, wax my eyebrows, wax my upper lip, shave, do a full face of makeup. Hopefully put extensions in,
去角质，给我的眉毛上蜡，给我的上唇上蜡，刮胡子，做一个完整的化妆。希望能做些扩展，
get my nails done, get my toes done, we're gonna do the most." And yes, I know people often claim
修好我的指甲，修好我的脚趾，我们会做得最多。” 是的，我知道人们经常说
that these transformations are for self-love and not others but I'm highly suspicious of
这些转变是为了自爱，而不是为了其他人，但我非常怀疑
how changing so much of your physical appearance is self-love. Sure you will feel more confident,
如何改变你的外表是自爱。当然你会感到更自信，
but it's because you now feel more desirable to others. We're always so concerned with being loved
但这是因为你现在觉得别人会更喜欢你。我们总是那么关心被爱。
I know it's a popular joke for people to comment things like "throwing myself off of the empire
我知道这是个流行笑话诸如 “把自己从帝国
state building" or "eating glass for breakfast" under happy couple posts and it's funny, okay,
大厦扔下” 或 “早餐吃玻璃” 之类的留言在幸福的夫妻的帖文底下。
don't get me wrong. But it's funny because we feel that there is a level of truth to it. Seeing other
我承认，这些留言·很好笑，不要误会我的意思。但这鞋留言好笑的原因就是因为我们觉得有一定程度的事实。看到其他
people in happy relationships prompts us to feel sad or slightly jealous that we are not being
人都在那么幸福的关系中，会让我们感到难过或有点嫉妒，因为我们没有得到
loved enough. Rarely do they ever make us think about how we can improve as a lover and maybe help
足够的爱。他们很少让我们思考如何变成更好的爱人，和也许可以助于
bring that kind of love into our lives. We seem to take our concept of love itself for granted. Most
把这种爱带入我们的生活。我们似乎认为我们的爱本身是理所当然的。
people assume that love is just intuitively known and it does not need to be learned.
大多数人们认为爱情只是凭直觉知道的，不需要学习。
Everyone will just naturally know what it is. But this stems from the problem of treating love
每个人都会自然地知道它是什么。但这源于将爱
as an object, a noun, a feeling something that just happens to us. Fromm and also Bell Hooks (RIP queen)
视为一个物品、一个名词、一种感觉就刚好发生在我们身上。弗洛姆和贝尔胡克斯（安息女王）
say we need to shift our perspective and understand love as an activity. Fromm actually
说我们需要转变观点，将爱理解为一种活动。弗洛姆实际上
calls love an art, and just like being good at any art such as playing an instrument, dancing, painting,
把爱称为一门艺术，就像擅长任何种艺术，想演奏乐器、跳舞、画画一样。
it requires constant practice, dedication, and faith. Just as how you can't be a good piano player by
它需要不断的练习、奉献和信念。就像你只在喜欢的时候练钢琴的话，绝对不能成为一个好的钢琴家。
only playing when you feel like it, you can't be good at love if you only choose to love when it is
同样的概念，如果你只有在你觉得方便的事后爱，你不会变成好的爱人。
convenient and enjoyable for you. Fromm also says that an art requires faith. When you practice an
弗洛姆还说，艺术需要信仰。当你练习一门艺术时，
art, and you run into a difficult skill rather than give up because it's hard. You have to have faith
你遇到了困难的事情，而不是因为它很难而放弃。你必须对
in eventually succeeding and dedicate effort to that art until you succeed. The same is with
对成功有信心，并为这门艺术付出努力，直到你成功。 爱情也是如此。
love. I'll get more into this later on with the overuse of the term "red flags" but i feel like
稍后我还会多谈这个主题，包括将通过过度使用 “危险信号” 这个词，但我觉得
people start to doubt their whole relationship just because they saw one random person on TikTok
很多人开始怀疑他们的整个关系，就因为他们在 TikTok 上看到一个随机的人
say something. Of course, if there's constant cheating, lying, abuse, etc. These are clear signs
说了些什么。当然，如果经常有劈腿、撒谎、虐待等，这些都是
to leave. Wiring our brains to think about love as something active rather than passive is actually
离开的原因。让我们的大脑将爱视为主动而非被动的东西，实际上
really helpful in separating love from abuse and dishonesty. I want to read a passage from
真的饿会帮助我们把爱与虐待和不诚实区分开来。我想从
Bell Hooks All About Love that I really like. To begin by always thinking of love as an action
我非常喜欢的 Bell Hooks 的 All About Love读一段。首先始终将爱视为一种行动
rather than a feeling is one way in which anyone using the word in this manner, automatically
而不是一种感觉，这是任何人以这种方式使用这个词的一种方式，自动
assumes accountability and responsibility. We are often taught we have no control over our
承担责任和责任。我们经常被教我们无法控制自己的
feelings, yet most of us accept that we choose our actions. That intention and will inform what we do.
感受，但我们大多数人都接受我们选择自己的行为。这种意图并将告知我们所做的事情。
We also accept that our actions have consequences. To think of actions shaping feelings is one way
我们也接受我们的行为会产生后果。考虑塑造感情的行为是
we rid ourselves of conventionally accepted assumptions, such as that one simply falls in
我们摆脱传统公认假设的一种方式，例如一个人在
love without exercising will or choice, that there are such things as "crimes of passion"
没有行使意愿或选择的情况下坠入爱河，存在诸如“激情犯罪”之类的事情，
i.e., "he killed her because he loved her so much". If we were constantly remembering that love is as love
即 “他杀了她，因为他非常爱她”。如果我们真的记得爱是什么意思，
does, we would not use the word in a manner that devalues and degrades its meaning.
我们就不会以贬低和贬低其含义的方式使用这个词。
I think that most importantly when you work on an art, creating a wonderful result is what leaves you
我认为最重要的是，当你从事艺术创作时，创造出美妙的结果会让你感到
with fulfillment, right? For instance, by finishing a beautiful painting, an artist bestows meaning
满足，对吧？例如，通过完成一幅美丽的画作，艺术家赋予
upon their life because the painting, as a product of the artist's efforts, reflects their incredible
了他们的生活意义，因为这幅画作为艺术家努力的产物，将他们不可思议的
abilities back onto themselves. The artist realizes that they are the reason why this canvas is so
能力反弹回到自己身上。艺术家意识到他们是这幅画布变得那么
beautiful. Thus, love is to nurture the flourishing of someone else and you recognize your own worth
美丽的原因。因此，爱是培育别人的繁荣，然后你
through their flourishing. If we treat love as an active art rather than a thing, love is about
通过他们的繁荣认识到自己的价值。如果我们将爱视为一种积极的艺术而不是事物，那么爱就是
giving rather than receiving. A lot of people think that giving equals sacrifice and that's why it's
敢于给去，而不是接受。很多人认为付出等于牺牲，这就​​是为什么这样
so honorable to do it. But Fromm says that giving does not have to require us sacrificing anything.
做感觉很光荣。但是，弗洛姆说，给予不一定需要我们牺牲任何东西。
When done for the sake of giving, and not some other goal, giving is actually the best way
当为了给, 而不是为了其他目标而付出时，给就是
to combat our existential loneliness. When you give you experience your own strength,
对抗我们存在的孤独感的最佳方式。当你给的时候，你就会体验你自己的力量、
energy, and aliveness. This is true when you give anything such as giving money or giving
能量和活力时。当你给
food to your children. But this is especially true in giving love because when you give
孩子钱或食物等, 任何东西时，情况都是如此。但在给予爱时尤其如此，因为当你给予
love, you give all the things that make up you. Your interests, your emotions, your passions your
爱时，你付出了所有构成你的东西。你的兴趣、你的情感、你的激情、你的
knowledge... quote "he enhances the other's sense of aliveness by enhancing his own sense of aliveness."
知识……引用 “他通过增强自己的活力感来增强他人的活力感”。
Sadly, in heterosexual relationships I still think this idea of the man being the giver and the
可悲的是，在异性恋关系中，我仍然认为男人是给予者，
woman being the receiver is present, and a lot of women happily endorse this idea because it's nice
女人是接受者的想法是存在的，而且很多女性很高兴地赞同这个想法，因为成为
and easy to be the receiver. My man should ask me to be his Valentine. He should be giving me flowers.
接受者很好也很容易。我的男人应该让我做他的情人。他应该给我花。
My man should be doing this and that for me. I see this sentiment get worse because of social media,
我的男人应该为我做这做那。我看到这种情绪因为社交媒体而变得更糟，
portraying perfect images of people's boyfriends. You know, the ones where a girl shows off all the
描绘了人们男朋友的完美形象。你知道，一那种一个女孩炫耀
sweet things her boyfriend does for her and the comments are filled with stuff like "my standards
她男朋友为她做的所有甜蜜的事情。通常，留言里充满了诸如 “我的标准
just got higher" "why doesn't my boyfriend do this for me" "if he wanted to he would" Again, the dominant
越来越高” “为什么我的男朋友不为我做这件事” “如果他想要做，他就会”
narrative here is that love equals being loved, which equals getting stuff. Of course, it feels
再次，这里的主要叙述是爱等于被爱，等于得到东西。
nice to receive things and it's important to have a lover that gives things as symbols of love. But
当然，收到东西的感觉很好，有一个爱人把东西当作爱的象征是很重要的。
ladies, basing love on what you receive makes love a passive commodity. You gotta focus on love as an
但是女士们，将爱建立在你收到的东西之上，就会让爱成为一种被动的商品。你必须把爱当作一种
action and give back. And giving love is not about giving material objects, it's about giving you as
行动，然后给回去。给予爱不需要时给礼物，而是给予你，作为一个人。
a person. Sharing your thoughts, your humor, your joy, and your sadness. That's what giving loveis.
分享你的想法、你的幽默、你的快乐和你的悲伤。这就是给予爱的意义。
One of the most loving couples i've come across are Hannah and Shane. They talk about how so many
我遇到的最恩爱的夫妻之一是汉娜和谢恩。他们谈论有多少
people pity Hannah as some poor sacrificial giver because they think she just gives without
人同情汉娜作为一个可怜的牺牲者，因为他们认为她只是给予而没有
receiving things we typically associate with love back such as traditional forms of pleasure. "One
收到我们通常与爱联系在一起的东西，比如传统的快乐形式。
time a woman who, uh, asked if I was shane's cousin.And he said no this is my girlfriend. And she
“有一次，一个女人，呃，问我是不是 shane 的表弟。他说不，这是我的女朋友。
like, came up to me and took my hands began to cry. And was like, that
所以她走到我身边，拉着我的手开始哭泣。
that's the most beautiful thing I've ever heard, like, you're an angel. Which was super
她跟我说了，“那是最美丽的我听说过的事情，比如，你是天使。” 这非常
uncomfortable, because that insinuates that I'm an angel because Shane is a terrible choice.
不舒服，因为这暗示我是天使，因为 Shane 是一个糟糕的选择。“
People wonder why Hannah, who has high social value as a pretty woman would partake in this unfair exchange.
人们想知道为什么 Hannah 作为一个漂亮女人具有很高的社会价值会参与这种不公平的交换。
It goes back to this dominant idea of love being finding the best bargain on the market. But
这可以追溯到爱是在市场上找到最好的交易的主导观念。但是
Shane and Hannah don't care about this dominant conception of love. They love
Shane 和 Hannah 并不关心这种主导的爱的观念。他们相爱
each other because they give their personhood to each other and they love the person they each
是因为他们把自己的人格给了互相，他们彼此相爱，但他们
are without primarily focused on what's in it for them. At this point, maybe you're like "Okay Oivia,
并不主要关注对他们来说是什么。在这一点上，你可能在想， “好吧，Oivia，
good job on becoming the most idealistic lover girl with zero connection to reality! As romantic
干得好，成为最理想主义的情人女孩，与现实的联系为零！
as giving for the sake of giving sounds, without care about receiving material gifts, we all want
虽然给予为了给，不在乎收到物质礼物这样听起来非常浪漫，我们都想
to feel loved. Doing the loving is so much effort and I'm too insecure to not crave being loved! Plus
感受到被爱。爱需要付出很多努力，我太没有安全感了，所以不可能不想被爱！另外
you can't just erase the value that material gifts have in our capitalist culture." And to
，你不能仅仅抹杀物质天赋在我们资本主义文化中的价值。” 对于
all that, I say, you are right. You are a hundred percent right, you got me, which is why proper
这一切，我说，你是对的。你是百分百正确的，这就是为什么正确的
loving is counter culture. It's near impossible because it's so opposed to how current culture
爱是反文化。 这几乎是不可能因为它跟我们现在社会的文化太不同了。
is. How can I focus on giving when I'm surrounded by people on social media
当我被社交媒体上的人们包围时，我怎么能专注于给予？
showing off what they receive? When our culture is so based on consumerism, on who has what, and
当我们的文化如此基于消费主义时，谁拥有什么，很
obviously I'm going to be obsessed with increasing my social value when that's how I'm constantly
明显，我会痴迷于提高我的社会价值，因为那就是我们不断被评判的方式……
judged... How can I dedicate that much time to practicing love as in art when society
当社会告诉我还有其他重要的事情要做 时， 我怎么能像在艺术中那样投入那么多时间给爱情呢？
tells me there are other important things to do? Like having a good career? I need to
例如，有一份好的事业吗？我需要
spend time on school and work so I only have time to practice love on a select number of
花时间在学校和工作上，所以我只有时间对少数
people. And for all these reasons that's why I say our conception of love is messed up.
人实践爱。出于所有这些原因，这就是为什么我说我们对爱的概念是一团糟。
According to Jean Baudrillard, we interact more with what he calls hyper reality than
根据让鲍德里亚，我们更多地与他所谓的超现实互动，而不是
reality itself. To explain what hyperreality is, I think it's best to just dive into one
现实本身。为了解释什么是超现实，我认为最好只是深入
of Baudrillard's examples. Consider the movie "Apocalypse Now", a film about the Vietnam War.
研究鲍德里亚的一个例子。考虑一下关于越南战争的电影《现代启示录》。
The acting, the special effects, the sets, the editing, everything about the film is made so
表演、特效、布景、剪辑，关于这部电影的一切都是为了让
that when we watch it on our screen it feels as real as possible. Heck, it becomes more real than
我们在屏幕上观看时感觉尽可能真实。哎呀，它变得比
the real war. Most of our understanding of the real Vietnam War comes from brief video clips online,
真正的战争还真实。我们对真实越南战争的大部分理解来自于网上的简短视频片段，
some news articles documenting the big highlights. Maybe a speech from some politician. But we have no
一些新闻文章记录了重大亮点。也许是某个政客的演讲。但是我们没有
real experience of the real Vietnam War. And the little bits and pieces we get from the news is
真正的越南战争的真实经历。我们从新闻中得到的点点滴滴是
an extremely watered-down version of the war. They tell us how many people died, shows short clips of
战争的一个极其淡化的版本。他们告诉我们有多少人死亡，展示了士兵战斗的短片
soldiers fighting, and innocent residents harmed. But what about the thousands of stories that go
，以及无辜居民受到伤害。但是成千上万个
unheard? The film "Apocalypse Now" ends up actually feeling more real than the real war. When people
闻所未闻的故事呢？电影《现代启示录》最终给人的感觉实际上比真实的战争还要真实。当人们
talk about the Vietnam War, they picture scenes from the movie rather than the actual war. The
谈论越南战争时，他们会想到电影中的场景，而不是实际的战争。 最初是对现实的模仿 的
media that was originally an imitation of reality ends up being more real, thus hyperreal. The hyperreal
媒体最终变得更加真实，从而变得超现实。超现实
was originally a copy of something real. But then we start to interact with the hyperreal
最初是真实事物的复制品。但是我们一点一点开始
more than reality, and so new forms of media end up imitating hyperreality rather than reality.
更多地与超现实而不是现实互动，因此新形式的媒体最终会模仿超现实而不是模仿现实。
It becomes a loop of copies, copying copies, copying copies, until our lives are looking
它变成了一个副本，复制副本，复制副本的循环，直到我们的生活正在查看
at copies of copies of copies. I believe Stephen West from Philosophize This! gave an example of
副本的副本。我相信来自 Philosophize This 的 Stephen West 举了一个例子，
how TV shows originally drew inspiration from real people in real lives, but over time new TV shows
说电视节目最初是如何从现实生活中的真实人物中汲取灵感的，但随着时间的推移，新的电视节目会
became inspired by past TV shows. Creating shows that are now completely detached from reality.
受到过去电视节目的启发。创作现在完全脱离现实的节目。
For instance, How I met your mother or Friends, comes out and we in real life start to frame what
例如，《我是如何认识你的母亲》或 《朋友》出来以后，我们在现实生活中开始
happens to us in relation to these TV shows. We create character tropes all the time, that we then
构想与这些电视节目相关的发生在我们身上的事情。我们一直在创造角色比喻，然后
form our real relationships around. Such as people saying, "I want to be just like Lily and Marshall or
我们在周围形成真正的关系。比如人们说，“我想像莉莉和马歇尔或
Monica and Chandler." We see people have magical love at first sight moments on screen and then
莫妮卡和钱德勒一样”。我们看到人们在屏幕上一见钟情就产生了神奇的爱，然后
build expectations of having the same magical feeling in real life. "I would be forever wed..."
建立了在现实生活中拥有同样神奇感觉的期望。 “我将永远结婚……”
The imaginary dictates reality. These expectations and tropes constrain us in thinking love needs to
想象支配着现实。这些期望和比喻使我们认为爱情需要以
be a certain way, or that if we start off as the hyper girlfriend, calm boyfriend trope we
某种方式进行，或者如果我们从开朗女友，冷静的男友这个观念开始，
need to maintain that trope. But the thing is, these expectations and tropes are not based in
就会需要保持这种比喻。但问题是，这些期望和比喻并非基于
reality. Now how does everything we've talked about apply to common phrases online? Let's start with
现实。现在我们讨论的所有内容如何适用于在线常用短语？让我们从
"if he wanted to he would". Two things about this mindset bother me. One, it builds the expectation
“如果他愿意，他就会做” 开始。关于这种心态的两件事困扰着我。第一，它建立了这样一种期望，
that our partners, specifically men, should know what to do and know what we want without us
即我们的爱人，特别是男性，应该知道该做什么，知道我们想要什么，不需要我们跟他们沟通。
communicating it. Two, as many people have pointed out it's literally contradictory. Girls say "if he
第二，正如许多人指出的那样，这实际上是自相矛盾的。女孩说 “如果他
wanted to he would" and so they don't tell their man what they want because he should just do
愿意，他就会”，所以她们不会告诉他们的男人他们想要什么，因为如果他愿意，他应该这样做
it if he wants to, but then if guys had the same mindset then they would not make the first move
，但是如果男人有同样的心态，那么他们 也 不会迈出第一步
either because they're thinking "if she wanted to, she would." And so no one would do anything.
因为他们在想 “如果她愿意，她就会”。所以没有人会做任何事情。
Also, sometimes people want to do things but are not sure if they should are scared, anxious, shy
此外，有时人们想做某事，但不确定他们是否应该，因为他们害怕、焦虑、害羞
or maybe they value your input. Which I really hope they do. Communication is so, so important.
或者他们重视您的意见。我真的希望是这样。沟通太，太，太重要了。
If you truly love someone, you would not base your partner's worth on whether they give you exactly
如果你真的爱一个人，你不会把你的爱人的价值建立在他们是否给
what you want. You would care about how much you're giving them and whether you're both having
了你想要的东西上。你会关心你给了他们多少，以及你们是否有
a reciprocal relationship. Before Valentine's Day, I saw quite a few TikToks talking about
互惠关系。情人节前，我看到不少抖音在谈论
how women in heterosexual relationships should wait to see if their man does something romantic
异性恋中的女性应该等待，看看他们的男人是否为他们做了一些浪漫
for them without saying anything, or if you do say something you should only mention it once. If your
的事情而不需要这个女人说什么，或者如果你说什么的话你应该只提一次。如果你的
man doesn't do anything or forgets that thing you had said once, it's a sign to end the relationship.
男人什么都没做，或者忘记了你曾经说过的话，那就是结束这段关系的迹象。
"And they know that it's important to you, you would only have had to say it once, right?
“他们知道这对你很重要，你只需要说一次，对吗？
Because if they loved you they would remember things that were important to you and it would be
因为如果他们爱你，他们会记住对你很重要的事情，
important to them too. Move in silence on Valentine's Day. Don't say anything. Hide the gift
对他们也很重要。在情人节那天默默地走一天。什么都别说。隐藏
you're getting them, hide the things that you're doing for them, not in a manipulative way. Just wait.
你得到他们的礼物，隐藏你为他们做的事情，而不是以操纵的方式。等待。
If you walk away from that day disappointed, feeling unappreciated, feeling alone, feeling like
如果你从那天离开时失望，感到不被欣赏，感觉一个人，感觉
they're right. it's just a day. It's commercialized. It doesn't mean anything. They show me they
他们是对的。这只是一天。它被商业化了。这没有任何意义。他们
love me every day, so it doesn't really matter. And I do care about them and I do...
每天都向我表明他们爱我，所以这并不重要。我确实关心他们，我关心……
Stop, okay." The thing that bugged me the most is that these TikToks would say, even if he shows
停下，好吧。” 最让我烦恼的是，这些TikToks会说，即使他
you that he loves you every other day, if he misses the mark on this one commercialized, arbitrary day,
每一天就向你表明他爱你，如果他在这个商业化的、任意的日子里错过了标记，
then sorry he clearly doesn't love you. There is so much concern around what can my man do for me,
那么对不起，他不爱你。 我的男人能为我做些什么，
can he meet my standards, that this one day can determine the trajectory of the rest of your
他是否符合我的标准，这一天可以决定你们关系的下场……？
relationship? I know it's different for everyone, maybe your boyfriend has amazing memory and grew
我知道每个人都不一样，也许你的男朋友记忆力很好，
up in a loving environment. But for my boyfriend and I, we both have a lot going on in our lives
在充满爱的环境中长大。但是对于我和我的男朋友来说，我们的生活中都有很多事情发生
And so it's unreasonable to expect us to remember something someone said once. Just because I forget
所以期望我们记住某人曾经说过的话是不合理的。就因为我忘记
that he wanted a poke bowl today for dinner, does not mean he's not important to me. My
了他今天晚餐想要一个poke 碗，并不是他对我不重要。
boyfriend also grew up in a household without much celebratory spirit. He didn't receive gifts for
我男朋友也是在一个没有太多庆祝精神的家庭中长大的。他没有收到
his Birthday, for Christmas. Him and his friends never even exchange gifts on special occasions
生日礼物和圣诞节礼物。他和他的朋友们甚至在特殊场合从不交换礼物
and so is it really fair for me to judge his love based on what he gives me if he has never
，所以如果他从来没有
been taught to give material gifts? Even as I'm saying this i understand how hard it can be to
被教导过送礼，我真的可以根据他给我的东西来判断他的爱吗？即使我这么说，我也明白
not let these little things affect you. We are surrounded by people who post picture perfect
不让这些小事影响你是多么困难。我们被那些发布他们关系的完美时刻的人所包围，
moments of their relationship and it constantly makes us fixate on how good the love we receive is.
这让我们不断地关注我们收到的爱有多好。
We are convinced that we should never settle, that there is some person out there who will give us a
我们坚信，我们永远不应该安定下来，那里有一个人会给我们一个
love as perfect as the ones we see in films and TV shows. I experience this sometimes too, um, okay
像我们在电影和电视节目中看到的那样完美的爱。我有时也会遇到这种情况，嗯，好吧
that was a lie. I actually experience this all the time. One of my greatest fears is not being loved,
，那是个谎言。我实际上一直都在经历这种情况。我最大的恐惧之一就是不被爱，
so honestly this whole video is almost like a lecture to myself. I've definitely got a lot
所以老实说，整个视频几乎就像是对我自己的一次演讲。我在
to work on in the realm of love, so please don't think I feel superior to everyone because Iam not
爱情领域肯定有很多工作要做，所以请不要认为我比每个人都优越，因为我不是
but that's why it's important to have a good level of self-love. So that you can squash
，但这就是为什么拥有良好的自爱水平很重要。这样您就可以
paranoid worries about not being loved enough and judge your relationship with a more clear head. And
消除对没有得到足够爱的偏执担忧，并以更清晰的头脑判断您的关系。 请记住 ，
remember that these movies are not real, they are hyperreal. The love on your TV screen looks more
这些电影不是真实的，它们是超真实的。电视屏幕上的爱情看起来
perfect and more real than reality, so it makes you crave that hyperreality. But it is a mere copy.
比现实更完美、更真实，所以它让你渴望那种超现实。但它只是一个副本。
"Red flags" is another term that has gained immense popularity. I think it is absolutely important to
“红旗”是另一个广受欢迎的术语。我认为
watch out for red flags in a relationship but this term has gotten overused. People watch a
在一段关系中提防危险信号是绝对重要的，但这个词已经被过度使用了。人们在网上观看了
15 second clip online and suddenly everyone's got a psychology degree. Here's how author Kim
15 秒的剪辑，突然间每个人都获得了心理学学位。以下是作者金贝克如何
Baker defined red flags. Red flags are whispers from our intuition that something isn't quite
定义危险信号。危险信号是我们直觉的耳语，表明有些事情不太
right. A red flag is that sinking feeling we get in our stomachs when something bad happens. There are
对劲。一个危险信号是，当发生不好的事情时，我们会感到下沉。有一些
slivers of evidence usually showing up early on, that this relationship is not the right one for us.
证据通常会在早期出现，表明这种关系不适合我们。
A red flag warns that deal breakers are headed our way. Now I want to place emphasis on deal breakers,
一面红旗警告说，破坏交易的人正朝着我们的方向前进。现在我想强调交易破坏者，
something that we absolutely cannot tolerate or is too much effort to fix. Conversely, not knowing how
这是我们绝对不能容忍或需要付出太多努力才能解决的问题。相反，不知道如何
to cook or having a perm is not a red flag. That's just called "not your preference". Don't let random
做饭或烫发不是危险信号。这就是所谓的“不是你的偏好”。不要让
strangers who know nothing about your relationship control you and tell you what is a red flag. I hope
对你的关系一无所知的随机陌生人控制你并告诉你什么是危险信号。我希望
we all dedicate more time to thinking about how to love others, how to build self-love,  and avoid
我们都花更多的时间来思考如何爱别人，如何建立自爱，避免
letting hyperreal displays of love mislead us. You can like and sub, if you want. Leave a comment
让超现实的爱表现误导我们。如果你愿意，你可以喜欢和订阅。 如果需要，
if you want. Thank you so much for watching, let's keep talking and I hope to hear from you soon. Bye!!
请发表评论 。 非常感谢您的收看，让我们继续聊下去，希望很快能收到您的来信。再见！！
Captions by Julia M.
Gina P 的字幕。